* Solutions
    
    Solutions
    
    * [Consumer Data Strategy
        
        Build out a robust consumer data strategy](https://liveramp.uk/solutions/consumer-data-strategy/ "Consumer Data Strategy")
    * [Enterprise Identity
        
        Create a unified customer view with enterprise identity](https://liveramp.uk/solutions/enterprise-identity/ "Enterprise Identity")
    * [Marketing Impact
        
        Maximise marketing impact and innovation across the advertising ecosystem](https://liveramp.uk/solutions/marketing-impact/ "Marketing Impact")
    * [Cross-Screen Measurement & Analytics
        
        Power strategic advertising decisions with comprehensive cross-screen measurement and analytics](https://liveramp.uk/solutions/cross-screen-measurement-analytics/ "Cross-Screen Measurement & Analytics")
    * [Media Networks
        
        Unlock the brand-building power of media networks](https://liveramp.uk/solutions/media-networks/ "Media Networks")
    * [Clean Rooms
        
        Measure campaigns across walled gardens, channels, and clouds networks](https://liveramp.uk/solutions/clean-rooms/ "Clean Rooms")
    
    By Department

    By Industry

* Resources
    
    Resources
    
    * [Resource Centre
        
        Explore our content library for resources, videos and case studies.](https://liveramp.uk/resources/ "Resource Centre")
    * [Blog
        
        The latest industry-related insights, tips and trends to stay ahead of the market.](https://liveramp.uk/blog/ "Blog")
    * [LiveRamp University
        
        Learn about our on-demand training, and custom education sessions for LiveRamp products.](https://liveramp.uk/liveramp-university/ "LiveRamp University")
    
    * [
        
        EBOOK
        
        ### Maximise Value With AI; 5 Ways For Retailers and Consumer Brands
        
        Download Now](https://liveramp.uk/lp/eb/5-ways-retailers-brands-maximise-value-ai-eb-registration/)
    
* Company

* Privacy
    
    Privacy

Toogle search bar

* UK

Privacy Policy
==============

Welcome to LiveRamp UK Limited’s Privacy Policy
===============================================

LiveRamp UK Limited (‘LiveRamp’, ‘us’, ‘we’, ‘our’) knows the importance of privacy for individuals (‘data subjects’, ‘consumers’, ‘you’) and is committed to protecting your personal data (which may also be referred to as ‘the data’, ‘your data’, ‘data’, ‘information’, ‘personal information’), and ensuring full transparency. **Please be aware** that references to ‘LiveRamp,’ ‘us,’ ‘we,’ and ‘our’ may also include the use of our affiliates and/or service providers and subcontractors inside and outside of the EU/EEA.

In order to achieve this, we have created this Privacy Policy, which consists of various category pages, to better assist you in navigating and finding information about how we process your data. We use the term ‘process’ throughout our Privacy Policy category pages to mean any or all of how we collect, use, disclose, transfer, and otherwise process your data. You can go to each of our Privacy Policy category pages by clicking on the category page names below, as well as by clicking on linked references and menu selections for those category pages within the category pages themselves.

* Our [Website and Marketing](https://liveramp.uk/web-privacy-policy) page provides you with further information about what data we collect and use about you in connection with your visits to and uses of our website, as well as marketing communications sent directly to you from us.
* Our [Services](https://liveramp.uk/service-privacy-policy) page provides details about our uses of your data through our products and services that we provide to current and prospective clients and/or business partners, including marketing services.
* Our [Employee Recruitment](https://liveramp.uk/recruitment-privacy-policy) page addresses how and why your personal data may be used by us when you apply for a job with us.
* Our [Your Rights](https://liveramp.uk/privacy/your-rights/) page will assist you with learning more about how you can control LiveRamp’s collection and use of your personal information, and allows you to exercise your rights under the General Data Protection Regulation (‘GDPR’) in relation to our Privacy Policy’s Services category page.

This Privacy Policy, including each of its category pages, is provided in a layered format to help ensure your ease of use. You can always email us at: [\[email protected\]](https://liveramp.uk/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) for further information or to exercise your rights under the General Data Protection Regulation (‘GDPR’).

Whenever we refer to ‘personal data’ throughout our Privacy Policy and its category pages, we may mean either data directly or indirectly related to an individual, or pseudonymised data. Pseudonymised data is where the data has been rendered less identifying through technological measures so that it can no longer be attributed to a specific identifiable person without the use of additional information.

**Please be aware** that our websites are not intended for children under the age of 13, and we do not knowingly collect any personal data about children under the age of 13. Further, we do not knowingly collect any sensitive information (i.e., information about your or any data subject’s race, ethnicity, religious or philosophical beliefs, sexual orientation, sex life, political opinions, health, trade union membership, or genetic/biometric data) via this website.

**Further, please be aware** that our websites may contain links to third-party (i.e., not LiveRamp’s) websites, plug-ins, and apps. Clicking on those links or enabling those connections may allow third parties to collect or share data about you. We do not control these third-party websites and are not responsible for their activities or their privacy policies, and none of our Privacy Policy category pages apply to those third-party websites, plug-ins, and apps. When you leave our website by clicking any such links, we encourage you to read the privacy policy of every website you visit.

### EU Countries

Please select the link relevant to your country : [France](https://liveramp.fr/politique-confidentialite-produits-services/), [Germany](https://liveramp.uk/privacy-policy-germany/), [Italy](https://liveramp.uk/privacy-policy-italia/), [Netherlands](https://liveramp.uk/privacy-policy-netherlands/), [Spain](https://liveramp.uk/politica-privacidad/).

LiveRamp Contact Details
------------------------

If you have any questions about any of our privacy practices, please contact us or our data protection officer in any of the following ways:

By email to LiveRamp:

* [\[email protected\]](https://liveramp.uk/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

By post to LiveRamp:

* LiveRamp UK Limited, 1st Floor, Imperial House, 8 Kean Street, London WC2B 4AS

You have the right to make a complaint at any time by contacting the Information Commissioner’s Office (‘ICO’), who is the UK supervisory authority for data protection issues ([www.ico.org.uk](http://www.ico.org.uk/)). We would, however, appreciate the chance to address your concerns directly with you before you approach the ICO and ask that you please contact us first.

Platform
--------

Solutions
---------

Resources
---------

Partners
--------

Company
-------

* UK
